Out here, God don't pick no favorites
Carnage Park is a action, crime, horror film directed by Mickey Keating.
Part crime caper gone awry, part survival horror film, this 1970s set thriller depicts a harrowing fight for survival after a pair of wannabe crooks botch a bank heist
and flee into the desert, where they inexplicably stumble upon Carnage Park, a remote stretch of wilderness occupied by a psychotic ex-military sniper.
Vivian, played by Ashley Bell.
Wyatt Moss, played by Pat Healy.
Ellen San Diego, played by Darby Stanchfield.
Scorpion Joe, played by James Landry Hébert.
Sheriff Moss, played by Alan Ruck.
Travis, played by Larry Fessenden.
Carnage Park is a 2016 American crime horror thriller film
directed and written by Mickey Keating.
The film stars Ashley Bell, Darby Stanchfield, Pat Healy, and Alan Ruck.
Keating described Carnage Park as being a nod to films by Sam Peckinpah and Peter Watkins
that were made in the 1970s, and he built the film around that concept.
The film explores themes of robbery, kidnapping,
hostage, bank robbery, death game.
The tone is dark and intense.